Thank you for coming to the Clanpop concert today!
Today we have a lot of things to talk about.
See you at the next show! This is Saho Tanaka.
Nighttime and Idols
Now, let's move on to the third topic, "Otabuki". When I told you that I went on location with Nighttime and Idols before, you said that you are like an anime geek.
I'm also an idol geek and recently I've been into VTubers.
Recently, I'm into VTubers.
I'm also an idol geek and a VTuber geek these days.
For example, when it comes to idols
For example, I have a group that I'm into.
I've always liked Momokuro.
Oh, Momo Kuro.
I guess that's where it all started.
I've seen some cute idols on TikTok and YouTube.
I watch music videos on YouTube of idols that I think are cute.
I watch a lot of things.
But I think there are times when I'm with them at events.
Are you the type of person who actively asks to have your picture taken with them?
I think you're a little different from what I've heard.
I don't think so.
I wonder if it's okay? Is this a good time? I'm not sure.
I don't know.
I know that idols have their own routines and things to do. I was wondering if I might cause you any trouble.
I'm also a bit shy, so it's hard for me to go out there.
I'm kind of like a person who watches the stage from the corner of his eye, and then cries. I see.
Do you usually watch VTubers?
Yes, I do. When I'm at home, I basically turn on YouTube, and most of the time I watch VTubers' videos.
I mainly watch the videos of VTubers who are working for Niji-sanji-san's office, and I enjoy watching their videos, such as their distribution, or their official programs, such as the one that Niji-sanji is running.
You enjoy watching such programs.
Yes, that's right.
I watch VTubers and talk shows, live game shows, etc. What kind of genres do you like?
What kind of genres do you like?
Yes, I do.
I like to see what this person is doing with this game.
Then I tap on them.
I watch quite a wide range of games.
You don't communicate yourself? Like live video game broadcasts?
Oh, but I have done it before.
Yes, yes.
Live video games.
Horror games?
Well, I've done some live action. Oh, you've played horror games, and you didn't scream or anything?
No, I did not. When you distribute a game, you are watched and commented on, and everyone follows you,
I didn't scream, I just enjoyed the horror of it. It was more like enjoying the horror.
I'm sorry about that.
It's not a complaint, but you also have the temperament of an idol fan,
If you think about what you look for in an idol, it is a different kind of idol, isn't it?
Yes, they are. But even if you say "cheers," it's just a fake "cheers.
That's amazing. You are an idol lover.
I think I can say "No" to the common default image of idols.
I played a game called Ao-oni, which is an old game that has been played in real life for a long time,
You can probably see a lot of people cackling about it in other places, too.
I had already played it enough.
Then, I would rather enjoy solving riddles with others.
I thought it would be more comfortable to watch.
I see. I think that might be the right way to think about entertainment.
As a way of positioning yourself.
But it's scary. I'd like to see them cackle.
Really?
But when they catch you off-guard, they do let out a squeal.
Crying?
But if they are coming, they are coming, they are coming, and if they are coming, when they are coming.
I can't take my eyes off of you, can I?
I guess this is the place.
Mr. Popper likes Mr. Tanaka, too.
I understand.
So, the three elements that make Mr. Tanaka.
I mean, the anything-goes shop, the letter room, and the nerd drop-in room.
Yes, sir.
I don't know...
I can't feel your heart in every word you say, but...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
It's amazing, isn't it?
This program is...
Mr. Purple
Mr. Guggel
Brother of Matson wolf
Keisuke
Mr. Yurigorou
Thank you very much!
Next time: Tanaka Sisu Rules, Stand by!
Bye-bye